Neufeld, Maurice Papers /3007
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Series VI. MISCELLANEOUS
  - Sub-Series B. National Labor Relations Board Files
    - Thomas Willard Holland Manuscript (1 binder) (Box 62)
      1) December 1953 Typescript: National Labor Policy by Agreement. Five chapters on labor-management conferences from the first War-Time Truce of 1918 to the conferences from 1950 to 1953; 2) April 1953 Typescript: The Review and Appeals Committee of the National Wage Stabilization Board.; 3) May 1953 Typescript: Appendix to a Chapter on the Earlier Period of the Wage Stabilization Board. September 1950-May 1951. 15 appendices. (Chapter itself included.)
  - Sub-Series C. Thomas W. Holland
    - Other material in the binder (Box 62)
      1) A note from Anne Polisar, Holland's niece, forwarding the clipping described in (2) below. 2) Clipping from The Washington Post, May 17, 1984: "T.W. Holland, Veteran of U.S. Agencies, Dies." 3) Handwritten letter from Holland to Jean McKelvey, January 15, 1954. 4) Letter from Dallas L. Jones, University of Michigan, enclosing copies of letters between Walter Drew and James Emery. These letters were included in binder because of their relevance to Holland's Manuscript. 5) List of dates of Emery and Drew correspondence: 4 letters each.
    - Affidavit Compliance Section, 1948 (Box 62, Folder 1)
    - Cases Heard by Board (MFN present), 1948 (Box 62, Folder 2)
    - Fiscal, 1948 (Box 62, Folder 3)
    - Fiscal & Office Services, 1945-1948 (Box 62, Folder 4-5)
    - Forms, etc. (Box 62, Folder 6)
    - General Administrative Orders, 1948 (Box 62, Folder 7)
    - General Counsel & Field Operations, 1947-1948 (Box 62, Folder 8-9)
    - Injunctions, 1947 (Box 62, Folder 10)
    - Injunctions, 1948 (Box 62, Folder 11)
    - Legal, 1947 (Box 62, Folder 12)
    - Matters of General and Particular Information Legal Assistants to Board Members (Box 62, Folder 13)
    - New Releases, 1948 (Box 62, Folder 14)
    - Personnel, 1948 (Box 62, Folder 15)
    - Reorganization Plan, 1950 (Box 62, Folder 16)
    - Rules & Regulations, 1947 (Box 62, Folder 17)
    - Salaries & Expenses, 1947 (Box 62, Folder 18)
    - Salaries & Expenses, 1948 (Box 62, Folder 19)
    - ILR 70 Administrative Practices and Procedures, 1949 (Box 62, Folder 20-21)
    - Grievance Procedure ILR (Keggi Case) (Box 63, Folder 1)
    - Grievance Procedure ILR (Keggi Case) [cont.] (Box 63, Folder 2)
    - Friedman, Mark -- Corresp. (Box 63, Folder 3)
    - Faculty -- ILR -- Personnel Policy (Appointments & Promotions) II (Box 63, Folder 4)
    - Faculty -- ILR -- Personnel Policy (Appointments & Promotions) II [cont.] (Box 63, Folder 5)
    - Faculty -- ILR -- Pers. Pol. (Appt. & Pro.) (Box 63, Folder 6)
    - Dean -- ILR -- (Catherwood) (Box 63, Folder 7)
    - Dean -- ILR -- (Moore) (Box 63, Folder 8)
    - Courses -- ILR 606 (507) - Spring 1972 (Box 63, Folder 9)
    - Courses -- ILR -- 499 (Box 63, Folder 10)
    - Fac. -- ILR -- Pers. Policy Search Com., 1971-1972 (Box 63, Folder 11)
    - Fac. -- ILR -- Pers. Policy -- Hist. Search Com. 1980-81 Administration, 1980-1981 (Box 63, Folder 12)
    - Fac. -- ILR -- Pres. Policy Hist. Search Com. 1980-1981 -- Announcement Distribution (Box 63, Folder 13)
    - Fac. -- ILR -- Pres. Policy Hist. Search Com. 1980-1981 Candidates Selected (Box 63, Folder 14)
    - Fac. -- ILR -- Pres. Policy Hist. Search Com. 1980-1981 Candidates Selected Schedule in Ithaca (Box 63, Folder 15)
    - Morris --RESTRICTED (Box 64, Folder 1)
    - Brody --RESTRICTED (Box 64, Folder 2)
    - Brody --RESTRICTED (Box 64, Folder 3)
    - Brody --RESTRICTED (Box 64, Folder 4)
    - Neufield --RESTRICTED (Box 64, Folder 5)
    - Teaching Appts. --RESTRICTED (Box 64, Folder 6)
    - Contemporary Labor Problems --RESTRICTED (Box 64, Folder 7)
    - Neufeld --RESTRICTED, 1972-1973 (Box 64, Folder 8)
    - Confidential - CU Libraries, 1982-1987 (Box 64, Folder 9)
    - CU - Colleges - Schools - Architecture File, 1977 (Box 64, Folder 10)
    - Common Disc. (Box 64, Folder 11)
    - CU - Committees - Faculty Council Policy (Box 64, Folder 12)
    - CU - Coms. - Promotions & Appeals (Box 64, Folder 13)
    - CU - Admin. - Dismissal of Fac. MBRS. - Hartman Case (Box 64, Folder 14)
    - Cornell Univ. - Admin. - Dismissal of Faculty Members - Hartman Hearings - Monday, May 21, 1973 (Box 64, Folder 15)
    - NYS College of Agri. And Life Sciences - Prof. John D. Hartman (Box 64, Folder 16)
    - Cornell Univ. - Admin. - Dismissal of Faculty Members -- Hartman Hearings - Tues., May 22, 1973 (Box 64, Folder 17)
    - Cornell Univ. - Admin. Dismissal of Faculty Members -- Hartman Hearings - Sat., May 12, 1973 (Box 64, Folder 18)
    - John D. Hartman - Correspondence, 1947-1964 (Box 64, Folder 19)
    - Guide to documents Submitted to the Faculty Hearing Board by John D. Hartman - May 12, 1973 (Box 64, Folder 20)
    - Guide to documents Submitted to the Faculty Hearing Board by John D. Hartman - May 12, 1973 [cont.] (Box 64, Folder 21)
    - Guide to documents Submitted to the Faculty Hearing Board by John D. Hartman - May 12, 1973 [cont.] (Box 64, Folder 22)
    - Cornell Univ. -- In the Matter of John D. Hartman (Box 64, Folder 23)
    - CU -- Col. & Schools Arts & SC (Box 64, Folder 24)
    - CU - Coms - Profs - at large selection (Box 64, Folder 25)